AndreWilkinson

TECH SKILLS

Langue:

Python

Javascript

Ruby on Rails

HTML

CSS

Database:

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

MySQL

Sequel Pro

SQL Lite

PROJECTS

concepts.

Shoe Runners: A website for sneaker collectors. A group project in which I helped to delegate roles among members contributed API research, concept and direction of project.

Confucius says "if you choose a job you love you will never work a day in your life". The

markets for companies to trade, to studying social media habits of these companies to

see who will capture the hearts of the consumer. being a Web Developer makes it easier

to convey my knowledge in these areas by using RESTful techniques MVC and OOP

pursuit of knowledge has always been a fun hobby for me, between studying the

Version Control:

Github

EMPLOYMENT

Framework:

Express

NodeJs

Angularis

Django

Flask

Bootstrap

JQuery

2016 - present **RESIDENT DEVELOPER**- Coding Dojo

+ Team based problem solving using current frameworks, version control,

2006 - 2015 PEST CONTROL TECH- Orkin

- + Offered knowledge of chemicals, processes, quality control, maximized effective and timely solutions.
- + Utilized EPA standards to ensure customer safety.
- + provided technical training to staff.

2000 - 2005 SHIFT SUPERVISOR – Starbucks Coffee Co

- + Constantly expanded personal knowledge of coffee styles and varieties.
- + Assigned appropriate baristas positions depending on strength and customer flow.
- + Engaged customer loyalty by remembering personal preferences and allergy information.
- + Trained new team members with positive reinforcement, respectful and encouraging coaching.

SOFT SKILLS

High fiver/fist bumper

Hobbies:

Sneaker collector

Youtuber

Bonsai creator

Future Tech:

Phoenix and elixir

Erlang

IOS

Emberis

EDUCATION

2001 – 2003 NEW YORK CITY TECHNICAL COLLEGE

+ Computer art and advertising.